Wee-yah!
Leo brought us to the warehouse, left us in the
cold Trying to buy a story, that was never being
sold You looked at the archive, you looked at the
frame You made a fatal error, and you didn't know
the name You thought you bought a scandal, to put
out on the wire But all you did was throw a heavy
engine in the fire The angle of descent is
cutting through the black! The shields are
burning up and there is no turning back! The
telemetry is screaming, the temperature is
high! We're falling like a meteor across the
open sky. Friction. Burning through the
atmosphere. Friction. Everything is ending
here. A heavy thermal blanket, a superheated
glow. The absolute destruction of the only
world you know. You wanted a reaction. You
wanted the heat. I'm bringing down the fire to
the middle of the street. Friction!
I'm sitting in the chair while the television
plays Waiting for the suit to cut through the
haze You walk into the room with a clipboard in
your hand Making your demands like you own the
heavy band You cross out the lines, you tell us
what to do But you don't have a clue what the
metal's going through The angle of descent is
cutting through the black The shields are
burning up and there is no turning back The
telemetry's screaming, the temperature is
high We're falling like a meteor across the open
sky. Friction. Burning through the
atmosphere. Friction. Everything is ending
here. A heavy thermal blanket, a superheated
glow. The absolute destruction of the only
world you know. You wanted a reaction. You
wanted a heat. I'm bringing down the fire to the
middle of the streets. Friction!
You looked at the camera. You called for shot 12.
You pushed me to the edge of the broken shelf. You
made your demand. And you crossed the final
line!
She's my sister!
Friction, burning through the atmosphere
Friction, everything is ending here A heavy
thermal blanket, a superheated glow The
absolute destruction of the only world you know
You wanted a reaction, you wanted the heat I'm
bringing down the fire to the middle of the
street Friction
Burn the contract, burn it in the atmosphere!
Friction!